nursingcrib.com 2011-12-30

# Privacy Policy | Nursing Crib

You are here: [Home](http://nursingcrib.com/) / Privacy Policy

We respect your privacy and we are committed to safeguarding your privacy while online at our site [Nursing Crib](http://nursingcrib.com/). The following discloses the information gathering and dissemination practices for this Web site.

**Log Files**  
Like most standard Web site servers we use log files. This includes internet protocol (IP) addresses, browser type, internet service provider (ISP), referring/exit pages, platform type, date/time stamp, and number of clicks to analyze trends, administer the site, track user’s movement in the aggregate, and gather broad demographic information for aggregate use. IP addresses, etc. are not linked to personally identifiable information.

**Newsletter**  
If a user wishes to subscribe to our newsletter _(powered by Feedburner)_ , we ask for contact information such as name and email address. Out of respect for our users privacy we provide a way to opt-out of these communications.

**Cookies**  
A cookie is a piece of data stored on the user’s computer tied to information about the user. Our site don’t use cookies. However, Some of our business partners use cookies on our site _(for example, advertisers)_. However, we have no access to or control over these cookies, once we have given permission for them to set cookies for [advertising](http://nursingcrib.com/advertising/ "advertising"). You can choose not to accept cookies by modifying your browser settings. At any time, you may remove any cookie stored on your hard drive by deleting them in your browser’s settings section.

Google, one of our third-party advertisers, may add a cookie to determine targeted advertisements based on your preferences and your visit to our site and other sites on the internet. You can choose to opt out of Google’s use of cookies by visiting the [Google ad and content network privacy policy](http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html).

**Links**  
This Web site contains links to other sites. Please be aware that we are not responsible for the privacy practices of such other sites. We encourage our users to be aware when they leave our site and to read the privacy statements of each and every Web site that collects personally identifiable information. This privacy statement applies solely to information collected by this Web site.

**Advertisers**  
We use outside ad companies to display ads on our site. These ads may contain cookies and are collected by our ad companies, and we do not have access to this information. We work with the ad companies: Google Adsense, Axill etc. Please check their websites for respective privacy policies.

**Contact Information**  
If users have any questions or suggestions regarding our privacy policy, please contact us at:  nursingcrib[at]yahoo.com

**DISCLAIMER:** Comments expressed in this website are those of the readers and do not necessarily reflect the position of NursingCrib.com or any of its sister sites. NursingCrib.com does not knowingly publish false information and may not be held liable for the views of readers exercising their right to free expression. 

All articles in this site was meant for educational purposes only. We don't claim full ownership of the videos, pictures and some articles posted on this site. All other trademarks are the property of their respective owners.
